Finding Aid for the S. Charles Lee papers LSC.1384
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Photographs
  - Theatres
    - Vern Theatre. - Los Angeles, 1939-1941; Foyer (Box 7, Folder 8)
      The modern spiralling forms in the foyer ceiling are offset by the traditional gilt trim behind the banquette.
    - Vern Theatre. - Los Angeles, 1939-1941; Lobby (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Vern Theatre. - Los Angeles, 1939-1941; Proscenium (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Two strips of neon, one blue and one white, in the ceiling cove, illuminate the auditorium. Neon is on a dimmer, which creates a theatrical atmosphere as well as controlling the light during picture operation. Pairs of buxom nudes painted in shiny metallic paint fly along the wall toward the screen.
    - Vern Theatre. - Los Angeles, 1939-1941; Box office (Box 7, Folder 8)
      The curving forms of the box office echo others of the same era. The porthole motif appears burnished steel or aluminum entrance doors, the neon circles on the ceiling and the circle design in the terrazzo floor.
    - Vern Theatre. - Los Angeles, 1939-1941; Exterior night (Box 7, Folder 8)
      At night the entire front of the theatre, including the tower sign, was brightly illuminated.
    - Vern Theatre. - Los Angeles, 1939-1941; Exterior (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Lee developed a simplified design which relied on the porthole motif to evoke the streamlined character of the great ocean liners of the era. Note on reverse: Exterior, surfaced form concrete. Modern in appearance, it is three tones in color. The ribbed portion was created by casting concrete against corrugated forms.
    - Visalia Theatre. - Visalia, 1946-1949; Exterior night (Box 7, Folder 9)
      At night the brightly illuminated lobby, the large neon sign and the prominent illuminated box office all drew attention to the theatre.
    - Visalia Theatre. - Visalia, 1946-1949; Rendering, watercolor (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Lee's rendering of this small-town theatre on a corner site in Visalia shows a simple Streamline Moderne two-story building with glass block, tile, curved glass windows and butt-jointed glass box office windows. The flat marquee shows recessed downlights, almost the only feature retained in the final design.
    - Visalia Theatre. - Visalia, 1946-1949; Exterior (Box 7, Folder 9)
      The finished theatre conforms closely to the design of the night-time rendering. The box office and sign focus attention on the corner. The use of artificial brick cladding was fashionable for both commercial and residential building of the period. (See also the Garmar Theatre in Montebello 30301-30305 for similar treatment of the exterior.
    - Visalia Theatre. - Visalia, 1946-1949; Candy counter (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Lee's design for the candy counter incorporated the Streamline Moderne curves initially planned for the exterior. Glass, shiny stainless steel fixtures, curved blond wood veneers and downlights in the ceiling all contribute to the effect.
    - Visalia Theatre. - Visalia, 1946-1949; Auditorium (Box 7, Folder 9)
      The auditorium interior reveals Lee's use of the inexpensive Quonset hut truss system, also used in the Puente Theatre (51101-51110) and the Garmar Theatre ((30301-30305) from the same period. In the immediate post-war period the system was used to build housing, commercial and factory buildings to satisfy the pent-up demand for new construction.
    - Visalia Theatre. - Visalia, 1946-1949; Perspective sketch night (Box 7, Folder 9)
      This night view is a simplified design for a one-story building, retaining the downlighting in the lobby area, but eliminating the curved Streamline effects of the daytime view. Here the sign at the corner becomes the principal element of the design. Lee uses a series of recessed frames highlighted by indirect lighting, around the entire entrance, the poster cases, the false windows on the façade, and above the box office as a unifying motif.
    - Visalia Theatre - Visalia, Foyer (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Lee used the frame motif from the exterior as a central feature in the foyer to advertise coming attractions.
    - Vogue Theatre. - Hollywood., 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Poster display (Box 7, Folder 11)
      A narrow aisle between the glass wall and the poster wall allows access to change the posters. This photograph reveals that the glass wall is not curved, but instead is composed of a series of flat glass panes butt-jointed together to form a curved shape.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Perspective sketch, colored (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Lee's rendering for the Vogue Theatre, Vogue Market and Vogue Beauty Shop was executed almost precisely as initially conceived. The elaborate decorations on the tower are in the spirit of Art Deco, but the executed decorations are of a more traditional character. The interior spaces are more streamlined than the exterior design suggests. Both the name Vogue and the details of the interior suggest an elegant experience to the moviegoers of Southgate, an industrial working-class suburb of Los Angeles.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Exterior (Box 7, Folder 11)
      The clean lines, light-colored stucco finish and modern typography tie the theatre and retail spaces together.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Exterior night (Box 7, Folder 11)
      The bright marquee and the tower sign attract attention to the theatre at night. Lee used a similar design for the tower sign on the Tower Theatre in Compton (62701-62707) of 1935-1936.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Foyer (Box 7, Folder 11)
      The sweeping curves of the foyer are accentuated by the curves and circles of the panels of ceiling lights behind translucent glass and recessed into coves above the fixtures.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Lounge (Box 7, Folder 11)
      The lounge is furnished with an elaborate over-scaled Neo-Baroque banquette topped by a large mirror. Lee often used over-scaled traditional-style furnishings to offset the sleek modernity of the overall design.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Auditorium (Box 7, Folder 11)
      With plush upholstered seats, touches of gilt and glitter, formal pilasters, and the almost Japanese delicacy of a mural, Lee suggests an atmosphere of elegance to transport the audience from their daily lives.
    - Vogue Theatre. - South Gate, 1937-1938; Lobby, box office (Box 7, Folder 11)
      The curved lines of the design of the terrazzo floor are echoed in the curved wall of the lobby. The posters cases are located behind a wall of glass (71105).
  - Residences
    - Wasco Theatre - Wasco. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Apartments [French] - concept, Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments [Deco] - concept, Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments Bruce Arms - Los Angeles, Exterior, 532 S. Hobart, Los Angeles (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments, Exterior (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments [Moderne]. - concept, 1938; Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Associates Incorporated Apartment - Beverly Hills. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Associates Incorporated Residence - Burbank. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Exterior (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Living room (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Bedroom (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Stairway (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Tod Browning, Beverly Hills. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - El Mirador Apartments [California Builders] - Hollywood, Entry (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - El Mirador Apartments [California Builders] - Hollywood, Setting (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - El Mirador Apartments [California Builders] - Hollywood, Exterior (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Cohen House [M.M. Cohen] - Los Angeles, Facade (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cohen House [M.M. Cohen] - Los Angeles, Entry close-up (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cummings House, Exterior view (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Davis Residence - Monrovia. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Deutch Residence. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Eudemiller Residence. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Sun room (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Exterior front (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Exterior side elev. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Dining room (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Living room (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Bedroom (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Kitchen (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Houses. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hungerford (Leo) Residence - Los Angeles. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Hunt (Phillip) Residence. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Jacob Kalb (Du Barry Apartment. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - King. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Kornhandler. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Community room (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Apt interior, bedroom (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Apt interior, dining room (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Lobby desk (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Writing room (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Lobby (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Exterior view (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Courtyard, fountain (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Dining room (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Living room (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Entrance elevation, sketch (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Exterior view, garden elev. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Exterior view, entrance (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Living room (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Pacht (Isaac) Residence - Los Feliz?. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Camrose Apartments (Phillips) - Hollywood. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Dining room (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Entry (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Kitchen (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Bathroom (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Built-in radio-phonograph? (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Fireplace (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Dining room (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Concealed bar, opened (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Living room (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Bedroom (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sherman (J.W.) Residence - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Silbert (Bruce Arms) Apartment. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Simon Residence - Beverly Hills. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Troyer Brothers apartment. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Universal Holding Company (Lexington Manor Apartments). (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Universal Holding Company duplexes - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925-26; Principal elevation, on linen (Box 172)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925-26; Detail, elevator door frame (Box 172)
  - Commercial Buildings
    - Mayer Investment (Hollywood - Western Building) - Hollywood, Pencil sketch, perspective, with pastel
    - Max Factor Building. - Hollywood, 1935; Sheet 2 Sections, interior details
    - Max Factor Building. - Hollywood, 1935; Rev. Floor Plan Sheet 1A-A
    - Max Factor Building. - Hollywood, 1935; Detail Sheet 12
    - Max Factor Building. - Hollywood, 1935; Elevation Sheet 1-Job 351,352
      This elevation drawing shows Lee's Art Deco styling of the Max Factor building façade, which he repeated in his designs for showrooms and furniture. Photographs in the Lee archive show that his remodeling included stylish showrooms planned to complement the complexions and hair coloring of clients, and also a paneled office for the company's chief executive.
    - Max Factor Building. - Hollywood, 1935; Floor plan Sheet 1B
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Neon parking sign, ink/pastel? on tissue
    - Aero Supplies of Los Angeles, Incorporated. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Airplane Club., 1936.; Perspective sketch (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Baby Shop. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ball Building - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Staber's Beauty Shop [Dr. Barton], Storefront (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Berkoff (Dr. Louis) Building - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Blink (R.L.). (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - B'nai B'rith (Beverly Hills Lodge) - Beverly Hills. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Bowling Alleys. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Bridge Club. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Building - Huntington Park. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Carv-Arts, Storefront (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Darby Company factory building. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - De Mille [Store Building], Exterior (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - De Mille [Store Building], Rendering (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Lee (Don) Cadillac Showroom. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Easterday Supply Company Factory. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Epstein Building. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Esnard (Paul) Professional Building. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Chrysler Showroom [Fred Fudge]. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - General Water Heater - Hollywood, Perspective sketch (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - General Water Heater Building - Hollywood, Bird's eye rendering (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - General Water Heater Building - Hollywood. (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - General Water Heater - Hollywood, Façade (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Globe Department Store. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Greene ' Hinkle Store - Beverly Hills. (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Cocktail lounge (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Bowling area (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Exterior (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Spectator seats (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Perspective sketch (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Luncheonette (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Inside view of front entrance (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Bowling alleys (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Pylon sign (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tower Bowl (A.J. Hanson) Bowling Alley - San Diego, Exterior night (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Harn of California. (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Hilton (E.G.) Automobile Showroom. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Exterior rendering (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Kitchen (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Interior rendering, lunch counter, Wayne McAllister, Associate (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Interior rendering, bar, Wayne McAllister, Associates (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Interior rendering, booths, Wayne McAllister, Assoc. (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Booths (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Bar (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Lunch counter (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Melody Lane Restaurant - [Hollywood ' Vine], Hollywood, Interior rendering, stair, Wayne McAllister Assoc. (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Harwin's Jewelers [Carl Horwitz]., 1944.; Facade (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Harwin's Jewelers [Carl Horwitz]., 1944.; Perspective sketch (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Harwin's Jewelers [Carl Horwitz]., 1944.; Interior (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Horwitz Market - Van Nuys. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Hosiery Finishers, Incorporated - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Houston (W.W.) Factory. (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - International Business Machines. (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Fairfax Storage [Carl Jacobs]. (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Kolmitz - Westwood, Perspective sketch, storefront (Box 10, Folder 1)
      The Lee collection contains a number of photographs of theatres that Lee was charged with remodeling. This series of photos of a turn-of-the-century vaudeville theatre illustrates by contrast the innovations developed by architects for motion picture theatres. The entry to these older theatres was often off the street, through a long hallway. Advertising displays were merely cardboard signs.
    - Desert Club [La Quinta Development] - La Quinta, Lounge (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Desert Club [La Quinta Development] - La Quinta, Restaurant (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Desert Club [La Quinta Development] - La Quinta, Pool (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Desert Club [La Quinta Development] - La Quinta, Bird's eye rendering (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Desert Club [La Quinta Development] - La Quinta, Rendering, 2nd unit (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Landau Building., 1927.; Perspective sketch (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Lawson. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Laykin et Cie. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Le Roy's [Le Roy Diamond] - Los Angeles, Before remodel; Remodeled facade (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Lee (S. Charles) Office Building, Facade (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Pool, George Murphy (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Exterior (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Playhouse (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Courtyard, George Murphy, Nancy Carroll (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Dining room (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Bedroom (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Lounge (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hotel del Tahquitz [Thomas Lipps] - Palm Springs, Bar (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Malsman (S.)- [Burton ' Company] - Los Angeles. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Marchetti's Restaurant - [Los Angeles?], Dining room (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Marchetti's Restaurant - [Los Angeles?], Exterior (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Marchetti's Restaurant - [Los Angeles?], Perspective sketch (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Mattel Creations, Incorporated. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Makeup room (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Showroom (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Remodeled facade (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Exterior, before remodel (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Plan (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Make-up Studio entrance, exterior (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Office entrance (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Make-up Studio entrance, interior (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Building - Hollywood, Model (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Max Factor Factory, Mexico. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Mellos Factory. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Milani Foods Incorporated Plant. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Commercial Buildings. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Morrell (John) ' Company. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Mayer Investment (Hollywood - Western Building) - Hollywood, Perspective sketch (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Mayer Investment (Hollywood - Western Building) - Hollywood, Exterior view (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Mayer Investment (Hollywood - Western Building) - Hollywood, Exterior, opening night (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Mayer Investment (Hollywood - Western Building) - Hollywood, Grand opening, Norma Shearer, Irving Thalberg, S. Charles Lee (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Left to right in the photo: Irving G. Thalberg, Leila Hyams, Moira Shearer, S. Charles Lee, Owen Lee, Raquel Torres, and Sidney Weisman, manager of the building.
    - Municipal Light Water ' Power - Los Angeles, Exterior night (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Municipal Light Water ' Power - Los Angeles, Floor plan (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Municipal Light Water ' Power - Los Angeles, Perspective sketch (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Municipal Light Water ' Power. - Los Angeles, 1932; Perspective sketch (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Office Buildings, [Miscellaneous projects]. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Office Tower [Gothic]., 1926.; Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Unbuilt concept
    - Office Building [I.C.Freud], Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
      This rendering is marked for Mr. I.C. Freud.
    - Office Tower [Moderne]., 1935.; Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Office Tower [concept], Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Office Building/Store, Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Office Building [corner tower], Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Office Building [block], Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic College Beauty Shop. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Prudential Insurance. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Republic Heater Corporation. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Revell Plastics. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Robinson (Louis) Medical Building. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Reid (Rose Marie) Factory. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Sanford Jacobi Building - Hollywood, Exterior (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Simmonds (J.) Store Building - Los Angeles. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Skouras (Charles) Office. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Southern Pacific Building, Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Steven's Stores, Facade (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Steven's Stores, Facade night (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Steven's Stores, Interior, shoppers (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Steven's Stores, Interior, shoppers (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Steven's Stores, Display window, night (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Stores - Westwood. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Thompson Stores. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Towne Talk. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Trabert ' Hoeffer Store, Facade before remodel (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Trabert ' Hoeffer Store, Facade (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Trabue - Pittman Building - Los Angeles. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Tropics., 1938.; Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Melrose Hotel [Troyer]. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Union Oil Gas Station, Perspective sketch (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Union Station. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Venice Brush Company - Venice. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Weinman Brothers Factory. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Weisman Medical Building. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Weisman Service Station. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Wholesale Plumbing Supply Company, Building front and remodeled bank (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Public/Institutional